<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.krdc.desktop</id>
  <name>KRDC</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KRDC</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KRDC</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KRDC</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KRDC</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KRDC</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Fjärranslutning till skrivbord</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KRDC</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKRDCxx</name>
  <summary>Connect with RDP or VNC to another computer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Connecta amb RDP o VNC a un altre ordinador</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Connect with RDP or VNC to another computer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Met RDP of VNC naar een andere computer verbinden</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Ligar-se por RDP ou VNC a outro computador</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Anslut till en annan dator med RDP eller VNC</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">З'єднання з іншим комп'ютером за допомогою RDP або VNC</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxConnect with RDP or VNC to another computerxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KRDC is a client application that allows you to view or even control the desktop session on another machine that is running a compatible server. VNC and RDP is supported.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KRDC és una aplicació client que permet veure o fins i tot controlar la sessió d'escriptori en una altra màquina que estigui executant un servidor compatible. Estan suportats VNC i RDP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KRDC is a client application that allows you to view or even control the desktop session on another machine that is running a compatible server. VNC and RDP is supported.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KRDC is een client-toepassing die u in staat stelt om de bureaubladsessie op een andere machine, waarop een compatibele server draait, te bekijken en zelfs te besturen. VNC en RDP worden ondersteund.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KRDC é uma aplicação-cliente que lhe permite ver ou mesmo controlar a sessão do ambiente de trabalho noutro computador que esteja a executar um servidor compatível. São suportados os protocolos VNC e RDP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Fjärranslutning till skrivbord är ett klientprogram som låter dig visa eller till och med styra skrivbordssessionen på en annan dator som kör en passande server. VNC och RDP stöds.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KRDC — це клієнтська програма, яка надає вам змогу переглядати і навіть керувати стільничним сеансом на віддаленому комп’ютері, на якому запущено сумісний з клієнтом сервер. З-поміж серверів у програмі передбачено підтримку VNC і RDP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKRDC is a client application that allows you to view or even control the desktop session on another machine that is running a compatible server. VNC and RDP is supported.xx</p>
  </description>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=krdc</url>
  <url type="donation">https://kde.org/donate/</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/stable5/en/kdenetwork/krdc/index.html</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org/applications/internet/krdc/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.kde.org/images/screenshots/krdc.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <update_contact>kde-devel@kde.org</update_contact>
</component>
